Guide to the Mabel Loomis Todd Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Subject Files, 1865-1932; Series VII; 9.25 linear feet (25 boxes)
  - Clubs
    - American Female Guardian Society, 1889, 1892, 1900, 1904, 1910 (Box 104, Folder 277)
    - American Forestry Association: correspondence, 1929-1930 (Box 104, Folder 278)
    - American Merchant Marine Library: correspondence, 1925-1932 (Box 104, Folder 279)
    - American Museum of Natural History: correspondence and printed matter, 1927-1929 (Box 104, Folder 280)
    - Amherst Historical Society
      - Correspondence, 1889-1899 (Box 104, Folder 281)
        See also: box 53, folders 7-8.
      - Correspondence, 1900-1909 (Box 104, Folder 282)
      - Correspondence, 1910-1919, 1929-1930, undated (Box 104, Folder 283)
      - History, 1899, 1917-1918 (Box 104, Folder 284)
        See also: box 76, folder 287.
      - Financial campaign, 1916 (Box 104, Folder 285)
      - Minutes, reports, 1900, 1903, 1915, 1917 (Box 104, Folder 286)
      - Newspaper clippings, lists, sketches and photographs, 1899-1931 (Box 104, Folder 287)
    - Amherst Shakespeare Club: stage instructions and lists of casts, 1890s (Box 104, Folder 288)
    - Amherst Women's Club
      - Correspondence, 1892-1907, undated (Box 104, Folder 289)
      - Printed matter, 1893-1909, 1928 (Box 104, Folder 290)
    - Arkansas Federation of Women's Clubs: correspondence, 1903 (Box 104, Folder 291)
    - Audubon Society, Coconut Grove: correspondence and printed matter, 1920-1931 (Box 104, Folder 292)
      See also: Scrapbooks, vol. X-XIII, boxes 87-88, folders 8-11.
    - Boston Authors Club
      - Printed matter, 1901-1909 (Box 104, Folder 293)
        See also: See also scrapbooks, vols. X, XI, and XIII, boxes 87-88, folders 8-9, 11.
      - Printed matter, 1910-1920 (Box 104, Folder 294)
      - Year Book, 1913 (Box 104, Folder 295)
      - Printed matter and correspondence, 1921-1932 (Box 104, Folder 296)
    - Coconut Grove Library Association: correspondence, 1928-1930 (Box 105, Folder 297)
    - Colonial Dames: correspondence, 1895, undated (Box 105, Folder 298)
    - The Columbine Society: correspondence, 1929 (Box 105, Folder 299)
    - Committee of 99, University of Miami Symphony Orchestra, 1931-1932 (Box 105, Folder 300)
    - Committee of 100, Miami Grand Opera Company: correspondence and invitations, 1926, 1929-1930 (Box 105, Folder 301)
    - Connecticut Valley Historical Society: correspondence and printed matter, 1903, 1906-1907, 1919-1923 (Box 105, Folder 302)
    - Cosmopolitan Club: invitations and notices, 1911-1913, 1927-1930 (Box 105, Folder 303)
      See also: box 86, folder 7.
    - Daughters of the American Revolution, Mary Mattoon Chapter
      - Report by Mabel Loomis Todd, 1894 (Box 105, Folder 304)
      - Address by Julia Ward Howe, 1899 June 3 (Box 105, Folder 305)
      - Correspondence, 1895-1929, undated (Box 105, Folder 306)
        See also: box 104, folders 281-287.
      - Printed matter, 1897-1914 (Box 105, Folder 307)
      - Printed matter, 1915-1925 (Box 105, Folder 308)
      - Printed matter, 1902, 1930-1931 (Box 105, Folder 309)
      - Programs, 1899, 1900, 1925 (Box 105, Folder 310)
        See also: boxes 86-87, folders 7-8.
      - Mabel Loomis Todd's notes, 1897, undated (Box 105, Folder 311)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1897-1918, 1934 (Box 105, Folder 312)
      - Miscellaneous printed matter and photographs, 1894-1911, 1929 (Box 105, Folder 313)
    - Everglades National Park Association: correspondence, 1929, 1932 (Box 105, Folder 314)
    - Ex Club: correspondence, 1906, 1911, 1913, undated (Box 105, Folder 315)
    - Florida Fellows of the Fine Arts
      - Notices of meetings, Undated (Box 105, Folder 316)
      - Correspondence and invitations, 1925, 1928, 1930 (Box 105, Folder 317)
    - Florida Society of Natural History: correspondence, 1927-1930 (Box 105, Folder 318)
    - Garden Club of Miami: correspondence, 1922-1927 (Box 105, Folder 319)
      See also: boxes 87-89, folders 9-12.
    - General Federation of Women's Clubs
      - Correspondence, 1894-1895 (Box 106, Folder 320)
      - Correspondence, 1896 (Box 106, Folder 321)
      - Correspondence, 1897-1900 (Box 106, Folder 322)
      - Correspondence, 1901-1913 (Box 106, Folder 323)
      - Miscellaneous printed material, 1892-1906 (Box 106, Folder 324)
      - Clippings, 1895-1908, undated (Box 106, Folder 325)
      - Miscellaneous notes, Undated (Box 106, Folder 326)
      - Fourth Biennial Convention, Denver, Colorado
        - Correspondence, 1898 (Box 106, Folder 327)
        - Printed matter, 1898 (Box 106, Folder 328)
      - Fifth Biennial Convention, Milwaukee, Wisconsin
        - Correspondence, 1900 (Box 106, Folder 329)
        - Printed material, 1900 (Box 106, Folder 330)
      - Sixth Biennial Convention, Los Angeles, California
        - Correspondence, 1902 (Box 106, Folder 331)
        - Printed material, 1902 (Box 106, Folder 332)
        - Newspaper clippings and badge, 1902 (Box 106, Folder 333)
      - Seventh Biennial Convention, St. Louis, Missouri
        - Correspondence, 1904 (Box 106, Folder 334)
        - Notes and manuscripts, 1904 (Box 106, Folder 335)
        - Notes, 1904 (Box 106, Folder 336)
        - Printed material, 1904 (Box 106, Folder 337)
      - Ninth Biennial Convention Boston, Massachusetts
        - Correspondence, 1908 (Box 106, Folder 338-340)
        - Printed material, 1908 (Box 107, Folder 341)
        - Printed material, 1908 (Box 107, Folder 342)
        - Reports and notes by Mabel Loomis Todd, 1908 (Box 107, Folder 343)
        - Official report, 1908 (Box 107, Folder 344)
        - Housekeepers' Club of Coconut Grove: correspondence, 1924-1928, 1931 (Box 107, Folder 345)
          See also: box 87, folders 8-9.
    - Key (Francis Scott) Memorial Association: correspondence, notes, and printed matter, 1908-1910 (Box 107, Folder 346)
    - Lady Wolverton Guild: correspondence, 1917, 1920, 1926, undated (Box 107, Folder 347)
    - Maine Federation of Women's Clubs: correspondence, 1912 (Box 107, Folder 348)
    - Mana-Zucca Music Club: invitations, 1931 (Box 107, Folder 349)
    - Massachusetts Federation of Women's Clubs
      - Correspondence, 1895-1896 (Box 107, Folder 350)
      - Correspondence, 1897 January-March (Box 107, Folder 351)
      - Correspondence, 1897 April-November (Box 107, Folder 352)
      - Correspondence, 1898-1900 (Box 107, Folder 353)
      - Correspondence concerning breakfast, 1900 October 3 (Box 107, Folder 354-356)
      - Correspondence, 1901-1907 (Box 107, Folder 357)
      - Programs, clippings, etc., 1894-1907 (Box 107, Folder 358)
    - Massachusetts Forestry Association, 1913 (Box 107, Folder 359)
    - Miami Women's Club: correspondence, clippings, notices of meetings, 1925-1931 (Box 107, Folder 360)
    - Missouri Federation of Women's Clubs: correspondence, 1904 (Box 107, Folder 361)
      See also: box 14, folder 338.
    - National League of American Pen Women: correspondence and printed matter, 1927-1929 (Box 107, Folder 362)
    - National Woman's party: press releases, 1916 (Box 107, Folder 363)
    - Ohio Federation of Women's Clubs: correspondence and printed matter, 1903-1908 (Box 108, Folder 364)
    - Pan American Institute: program, 1933 (Box 108, Folder 365)
    - Quest Society of Florida: correspondence, 1931 (Box 108, Folder 366)
    - St. Stephen's Church, Coconut Grove: correspondence, budget and notices of meetings, 1922-1931 (Box 108, Folder 367)
    - Vermont Federation of Women's Clubs: correspondence and printed matter, 1903 (Box 108, Folder 368)
    - George Washington Memorial Association: printed matter, 1910 (Box 108, Folder 368a)
    - Wisconsin Federation of Women's Clubs: correspondence, 1903, 1911 (Box 108, Folder 369)
    - Woman's Club of Coral Gables, Florida: correspondence, Undated (Box 108, Folder 370)
    - Women's Navy league: invitations, 1917 (Box 108, Folder 371)
    - Club membership cards and certificates, 1885-1932 (Box 108, Folder 372)
    - Unidentified: agenda and membership list, [1917] (Box 108, Folder 372a)
  - Wedding and Anniversaries
    - Wedding memorabilia, 1879 (Box 109, Folder 373)
    - 25th anniversary
      - List of names, 1904 (Box 109, Folder 374)
      - Scrapbook, 1904 (Box 109, Folder 375)
      - Correspondence, 1904 (Box 109, Folder 376)
    - 50th anniversary correspondence, 1929 (Box 109, Folder 377)
  - Sickness and Death
    - Loomis, Eben Jenks: condolence letters to Mabel Loomis Todd and David Peck Todd, 1912 (Box 109, Folder 378-379)
    - Loomis, Mary Alden
      - Condolence letters to Mabel Loomis Todd and David Peck Todd, 1910 (Box 109, Folder 380)
      - Condolence Letters to Mabel Loomis Todd and David Peck Todd, 1910 (Box 110, Folder 381)
      - Cards of condolence, florists' cards, miscellaneous, 1910 (Box 110, Folder 382)
    - Todd, Mabel Loomis
      - Convalescent exercises, 1913 (Box 110, Folder 383)
      - Notebooks kept by Mabel Loomis Todd while recovering from a stroke, 1913 (Box 110, Folder 384)
      - Nurses' notebooks on Mabel Loomis Todd's recovery, 1913 (Box 110, Folder 385)
      - Scrapbook on stroke and illness, 1913 July-1914 (Box 111, Folder 386)
      - Condolence letters to Millicent Todd Bingham, 1932 (Box 111, Folder 387)
      - Obituaries [AMS and TMS], 1932 (Box 111, Folder 388)
      - Newspaper accounts of Mabel Loomis Todd's death, 1932 (Box 111, Folder 389)
      - Eulogies of Mabel Loomis Todd, 1932 (Box 112, Folder 390)
      - Millicent Todd Bingham's notes on Mabel Loomis Todd's funeral, 1932 (Box 112, Folder 391)
      - Howard Hilder on Mabel Loomis Todd's Death, 1932 (Box 112, Folder 392)
      - Scrapbook No. 25, Death in Maine, 1932 October 14 (Box 112A, Folder 393)
      - Correspondence on the Mabel Loomis Todd Memorial fund, 1933 (Box 112, Folder 394)
      - Photographs of and correspondence about Mabel Loomis Todd's grave, 1933 (Box 112, Folder 395)
  - Social Life
    - Invitations, acceptances, regrets, calling cards, business cards, membership cards, 1881-1931 (Box 113, Folder 396)
    - Reception at Mrs. J.L. Grandin's in Boston: acceptances, regrets, related memorabilia, 1916 December 15 (Box 113, Folder 397)
    - Celebration of Emily Dickinson's one hundredth birthday: correspondence, 1930 (Box 113, Folder 398-399)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1917, 1920-1930 (Box 113, Folder 400)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1930-1931 (Box 113, Folder 401)
    - Programs, 1924, 1931 (Box 113, Folder 402)
    - "Matsuba," invitations, 1918, 1923, 1927, 1931 (Box 113, Folder 403-404)
    - Recipes, Undated (Box 113, Folder 405)
  - Art
    - First drawings from nature, 1869 (Box 114, Folder 406)
    - Drawings, [pre 1870] (Box 114, Folder 407)
    - Miscellaneous oil paintings watercolors, and sketches, 1870-1890 (Box 114, Folder 408)
    - Mabel Todd's portfolio, 1872 (Box 114, Folder 409)
    - Floral Watercolors and oil, 1875-1876 (Box 114, Folder 410)
    - Oil paintings, 1876-1878 (Box 114, Folder 411)
    - "Complete" list of paintings for 1876-1882 (Box 114, Folder 412)
    - Oil paintings, Hampton, New Hampshire, 1883, undated (Box 114, Folder 413)
    - Paintings and drawings by Mabel Todd on her trip to Japan, 1887 (Box 114, Folder 414)
    - Japanese woodblock prints with notes by Mabel Loomis Todd, [1887?] (Box 114, Folder 415)
    - Monarch butterfly used as cover by Samuel Scudder on his book, painted by Mabel Loomis Todd, 1888 (Box 114, Folder 416)
    - Flower paintings, 1879 July (Box 114, Folder 417)
    - Art: newspaper clippings on art exhibits in which Mabel Loomis Todd participated, 1886 (Box 114, Folder 418)
    - Art: program of the Sauveur College of Languages and the Amherst Summer School, 1894 (Box 114, Folder 419)
    - Map drawn by Mabel Loomis Todd of the Amherst area, Undated (Box 114, Folder 420)
    - Sketches by Mabel Loomis Todd, Undated (Box 114, Folder 421)
    - Flowers, Undated (Box 114, Folder 422)
    - Oil Paintings, Hampton, New Hampshire, Undated (Box 114, Folder 423)
    - Flowers, birds, landscapes, Undated (Box 114, Folder 424)
    - Mabel Loomis Todd's favorite pictures, Undated (Box 114, Folder 425)
  - Music
    - Piano-Forte Primer, presented to Mabel Loomis Todd in 1865, Undated (Box 114, Folder 426)
    - Printed matter from the New England Conservatory of Music, 1874-1876 (Box 114, Folder 427)
    - Notes taken at the New England Conservatory of Music, 1874-1876 (Box 115, Folder 428)
    - Exercise books from the New England conservatory of Music, 1876 (Box 115, Folder 429)
    - Notebooks, 1877, 1879, 1881 (Box 115, Folder 430)
    - Correspondence course in harmony with Stephen A. Emery
      - Lesson book and printed matter, 1883 (Box 115, Folder 431)
      - Notebook, exercises, and correspondence, 1883 (Box 115, Folder 432)
    - Programs and announcements of concerts given by Mabel Loomis Todd, 1884-1893 (Box 115, Folder 433)
      See also: Series VI, Scrapbooks.
    - Notebooks, 1886, 1889 (Box 115, Folder 434)
    - Notes, exercise books, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 115, Folder 435)
  - Biographical Writings
    - Genealogical
      - Loomis family, 1906, undated (Box 115, Folder 436)
      - Wilder family, Undated (Box 115, Folder 437)
    - Biographical
      - Dictionary of American Biography: text, proof page, Undated (Box 115, Folder 438)
      - National Cyclopedia of American Biography, 1899 February 20 (Box 115, Folder 439)
      - Newspaper accounts of social life, 1879-1916 (Box 115, Folder 440)
      - Newspaper accounts, 1891-1932 (Box 115, Folder 441-442)
      - Article by Charles W. Moore (unpublished), and associated correspondence with Harper's, 1931 (Box 115, Folder 443)
      - Millicent Todd Bingham's notes for biography of Mabel Loomis Todd, Undated (Box 115, Folder 444)
      - Biography for 1886-1916 by David Peck Todd (typed, 17 pages, 2 copies), 1934 September (Box 115, Folder 445)
      - Sketches of Mabel Loomis Todd's life, [Circa 1927], undated (Box 115, Folder 446)
      - Correspondence re: interviews, publications, 1895-1931, undated (Box 115, Folder 447)
      - Reminiscences concerning others
        - Thoreau family, 1958 (Box 115, Folder 448)
        - Julia Ward Howe, [Circa 1910] (Box 115, Folder 448)
        - James and Persis Smith, Undated (Box 115, Folder 448)
      - Mabel Loomis Todd's chronology of her life, Undated (Box 115, Folder 449)
    - Autobiographical
      - Memoir
        - For period circa 1874-1881, "Semi-chorus" (1 rough draft, typed, 14 pp., 2 clean copies), [early 1920's] (Box 115, Folder 450)
        - [For 1874. Written later?] (MS pp. 12-20, typescript copy-2 pp.), [before 1913] (Box 115, Folder 451)
        - Childhood to 1876 (typed copy), [after1873] (Box 116, Folder 452)
      - Millicent's Life
        - Vol. I, 1879; Vol. II, 1880 (in four parts), 1879-1880 (Box 116, Folder 453)
          See also: box 46, folders 49-52.
        - Vol. III, 1881-1882; Vol. IV, 1883-1885, 1888, 1881-1888 (Box 116, Folder 454)
      - Diary excerpts and biographical notes by Millicent Todd Bingham, 1870-1897 (Box 116, Folder 455)
      - Autobiographical writings, Circa 1930 (Box 116, Folder 456)
      - Memorabilia
        - Printed, 1884, 1893, 1898, undated (Box 116, Folder 457)
        - Personal, 1891, undated (Box 116, Folder 458)
- Financial Records, 1882-1948; Series VIII; 3.25 linear feet (9 boxes)
  FINANCIAL RECORDS has five sections: Bills and Receipts, Checks and Bank Statements, Correspondence, Miscellaneous Records, and Property.
  Bills and Receipts is arranged chronologically.
  Checks and Bank Statements is arranged chronologically.
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by writer.
  Miscellaneous Records is arranged by type of document (i.e. tax returns, wills, etc,).
  Property is arranged by location (i.e. Observatory House, Matsuba, etc.).
  - Bills and Receipts
    - 1885, 1894-1896, 1901-1915 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 117, Folder 2-7)
    - 1916-1919 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - 1918 (Box 117, Folder 9-11)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 117, Folder 13-14)
    - 1920-1924 (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - 1920-1931 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - 1922 (Box 117, Folder 17)
      See also: box 125, folders 92-105.
    - 1922-1926 (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 118, Folder 19-20)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - 1925-1931 (Box 118, Folder 22)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 118, Folder 23)
    - 1929 (Box 118, Folder 24)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 118, Folder 25)
    - 1930-1933 (Box 118, Folder 26)
    - 1936 (Box 118, Folder 27)
    - Stock receipts, 1928-1933, undated (Box 118, Folder 28)
  - Checks and Bank Statements
    - Bank Statements
      - Bank of Biscayne, 1924-1926 (Box 118, Folder 29)
      - National Shawmut Bank of Boston, 1924-1925 (Box 118, Folder 30)
      - National Shawmut Bank of Boston, 1932 April-1933 July (Box 118, Folder 31-32)
    - Savings account passbooks, 1912-1930 (Box 118, Folder 33)
    - Checkbook stubs
      - 1885-1888 (Box 118, Folder 34)
      - 1886-1902 (Box 119, Folder 35)
      - 1903-1933 (Box 120, Folder 36)
      - 1911-1933 (Box 121, Folder 37)
      - 1918 (Box 122, Folder 38)
      - 1917-1921 (Box 122, Folder 39)
      - 1922 (Box 122, Folder 40)
      - 1922-1923 (Box 122, Folder 41-42)
      - 1924 (Box 122, Folder 43)
      - 1925 (Box 122, Folder 44)
      - 1925-(1926)-1927 (Box 122, Folder 45)
      - 1927-1929 (Box 122, Folder 46)
      - 1930-1931 (Box 122, Folder 47)
      - 1931-1932 (Box 122, Folder 48)
      - 1932-1933 (Box 122, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence
    - Aetna Insurance Co., 1926, 1930-1931, 1933 (Box 123, Folder 50)
      See also: Cook Insurance Company, box 123, folder 56.
    - American Express Co., 1905 (Box 123, Folder 50)
    - American Molybdenum Co., 1904-1908 (Box 123, Folder 51)
    - American Telephone and Telegraph, 1930 (Box 123, Folder 52)
    - Amherst Cemetery Association, 1906 (Box 123, Folder 52)
    - Amherst College, 1900, 1909 (Box 123, Folder 52)
    - Armstrong (Collin) Inc., 1913 (Box 123, Folder 52)
    - Atkinson, Edith M., 1925 (Box 123, Folder 52)
    - Atlantic States Warehouse and Cold Storage Corp., Undated (Box 123, Folder 52)
    - Bachrach Incorporated, 1929 (Box 123, Folder 53)
    - Bailey (F.O.) Co., Inc., 1930 (Box 123, Folder 53)
      See also: Remington-Rand Business Service, box 124, folder 71.
    - Bank of Biscayne, 1925, 1927 (Box 123, Folder 53)
    - Bank of Coconut Grove, 1923 (Box 123, Folder 53)
    - Bankers Trust Co., 1926 (Box 123, Folder 53)
    - Bingham, Millicent Todd, 1926-1931 (Box 123, Folder 53)
    - Bingham, Walter Van Dyke, 1923, 1927, undated (Box 123, Folder 54)
    - Boston Safe Deposit & Trust Co., 1926 (Box 123, Folder 54)
    - Bosworth, George E., 1925 (Box 123, Folder 54)
    - Bradford & Adams, 1925-1926 (Box 123, Folder 54)
    - Cambridge Savings Bank, 1933 (Box 123, Folder 55)
    - Camp Mavooshen, 1927 (Box 123, Folder 55)
    - Casco Mercantile Trust Co., 1923 (Box 123, Folder 55)
    - Chappell (J.F.) & Co., 1928 (Box 123, Folder 55)
    - Clark, Eleazer W., 1923 (Box 123, Folder 55)
    - Clifford (C.M.) Real Estate and Insurance, 1923 (Box 123, Folder 55)
    - Coconut Grove Bank & Trust Co., 1929 (Box 123, Folder 56)
    - Coconut Grove Water Works, 1932 (Box 123, Folder 56)
    - Colby (Charles B.) & Sons, Inc., 1926-1927, 1930 (Box 123, Folder 56)
    - Colorado-Wyoming Chemical Co., Undated (Box 123, Folder 56)
      See also: Western Alkali Company, box 124, folder 75.
    - Cook Insurance Co., Inc., 1931 (Box 123, Folder 56)
      See also: Aetna Insurance Company, box 123, folder 50.
    - Coral Gables, 1926 (Box 123, Folder 56)
    - Cuny, T., 1932 (Box 123, Folder 56)
    - Dade County Tax Assessor, 1929-1930 (Box 123, Folder 57)
    - Dade County Tax Collector, 1929 (Box 123, Folder 57)
    - Dakin, Arthur H., 1916 (Box 123, Folder 57)
    - Davison (Freeman I.) Co., 1902 (Box 123, Folder 57)
    - Eastern States Storage Warehouse, 1930 (Box 123, Folder 57)
    - Equitable Life Assurance Society, 1901-1932 (Box 123, Folder 58)
    - Equitable Securities Co., 1899 (Box 123, Folder 59)
    - First National Bank of Amherst, 1917 (Box 123, Folder 59)
    - First Trust and Savings Bank of Miami, 1922, undated (Box 123, Folder 59)
    - Florida East Coast Hotel Co., 1923 (Box 123, Folder 59)
    - Florida Power & Light Co., 1927, 1930 (Box 123, Folder 59)
    - Florida state taxes, 1927 (Box 123, Folder 59)
    - Grace (W.R.) & Co., 1909 (Box 123, Folder 60)
    - Groff, Ulysses G., 1926 (Box 123, Folder 60)
    - Guaranty Trust Co. of New York, 1922, 1927, 1931-1932 (Box 123, Folder 60)
    - Guaranty Trust Co. of New York: receipts, 1922-1934 (Box 123, Folder 60)
    - Hahn, Florence Perry, 1916 (Box 123, Folder 61)
    - Hall, Alfred S., 1923-1924 (Box 123, Folder 61)
      See also:box 38, folders 1106-1108.
    - Hall, Chester G., 1927 (Box 123, Folder 61)
    - Harris, Ellen S., 1925, 1932 (Box 123, Folder 61)
      See also: Miami Shores, box 123, folder 66.
    - Higginson, Mary, 1914 (Box 123, Folder 61)
    - Hilder, Howard, 1923, 1926, 1928 (Box 123, Folder 61)
    - Home Savings Bank, 1910, 1934 (Box 123, Folder 61)
    - Hornstein, Mary Jane, 1926 (Box 123, Folder 61)
    - James, Arthur Curtiss, 1918 (Box 123, Folder 62)
      See also: box 15, folders 354-362.
    - Kent, Everett E., executor of Esther F. Wilder's will, 1924 (Box 123, Folder 62)
    - Kilborne, R.S., 1911 (Box 123, Folder 62)
    - Lailer, Frank, 1924, 1926, 1927 (Box 123, Folder 62)
    - Lambert, J. Walter, Undated (Box 123, Folder 62)
    - Lands, Nathan, 1921 (Box 123, Folder 62)
    - Loomis Oil Association, 1919 (Box 123, Folder 63)
    - Lucerne-in-Maine, 1926 (Box 123, Folder 63)
    - McLendon, R.B., 1917 (Box 123, Folder 63)
    - Marsh (Jordan) Co., 1921 (Box 123, Folder 63)
    - Massachusetts Agricultural College, 1910-1911 (Box 123, Folder 63)
    - Medomak National Bank, 1927 (Box 123, Folder 63)
      See also: Nevada-Colorado Power Co., box 124, folder 70.
    - Miami Bank and Trust Co., 1921 (Box 123, Folder 63)
    - Miami Income Properties, 1925-1927 (Box 123, Folder 64)
    - Miami Memorial Association, 1925-1928 (Box 123, Folder 65)
    - Miami Realty Sales, Inc., 1925-1927 (Box 123, Folder 66)
    - Miami Shores, 1925-1926 (Box 123, Folder 66)
    - Miller, F.B., 1925 (Box 123, Folder 67)
    - Minott, S.L., 1928 (Box 123, Folder 67)
    - Moore (D.T.) & Co., 1920-1922 (Box 123, Folder 67)
    - Morse, Arthur W., 1917 (Box 123, Folder 67)
    - Murray, Peter, Gardener and Florist, 1908 (Box 123, Folder 67)
    - Nassau Stamp Co., 1930 (Box 123, Folder 68)
    - National Bank of the Republic, 1906 (Box 123, Folder 68)
    - National Shawnut Bank, 1908, 1918, 1925-1933, undated (Box 124, Folder 69)
    - Nevada-California Power Co., 1907-1917 (Box 124, Folder 70)
    - New York Security & Trust Co., 1894-1895 (Box 124, Folder 70)
    - Newton, Church & Hewitt, 1910, 1914 (Box 124, Folder 70)
    - Northeastern Corporation, 1919, undated (Box 124, Folder 70)
      See also: American Molybdenum Company box 123, folder 51.
    - Northampton Institution for Savings, 1934 (Box 124, Folder 70)
    - Noyes Brothers, 1921 (Box 124, Folder 70)
    - Perkins, Herbert F., 1920 (Box 124, Folder 71)
    - Pierce (S.S.) Co., 1926, 1931 (Box 124, Folder 71)
    - Raymond & Whitcomb Co., 1902 (Box 124, Folder 71)
    - Remington-Rand Business Service, 1930 (Box 124, Folder 71)
      See also: Bailey (F.O.) Co., box 123, folder 53.
    - Richards Brothers, 1916-1917 (Box 124, Folder 72)
    - Riggs National Bank of Washington, 1909 (Box 124, Folder 72)
    - Riviera Landscape Co., 1927 (Box 124, Folder 72)
    - Romeike (Henry), Inc., 1914 (Box 124, Folder 72)
    - Sahler, Mrs. A.F., 1914 (Box 124, Folder 72)
    - Schuber, W.B., 1918 (Box 124, Folder 72)